<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Hugo Hero Theme</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Hugo Hero Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Edge Kanban</title>
      <link>/work/edge_kanban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/edge_kanban/</guid>
      <description>Whole class visual progress charts originally based on kanban. How does a group of 7 teachers across various specialties experience the use of Edge Kanban in their student directed classes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/services/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Some in the agile in education movement have practiced agile in their software or corporate jobs and see its application in education. Some educators have bumped up against agile practices and started to pull its way of thinking and working into their classroom. Still other educators have built entire programs and schools around the idea.
Whatever led you here, we would like to welcome you into a community of agile practitioners who are all trying to figure it out - “it” meaning something different to different people, but in general, “it” being a way to reimagine school, and the practices of teaching and learning, in an iterative manner with fewer carrots and sticks and a culture of high frequency, low stakes feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECIS Schools</title>
      <link>/work/ecis_schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/ecis_schools/</guid>
      <description>ECIS member schools Individuals and collaborative teams at ECIS member schools are invited to send proposals that document practices in:
Natural feedback (students receive feedback as a direct result of their work, e.g. a robot controlled garden grows healthy plants, not drying out or flooding); Non-traditional formative feedback (e.g. from peers, through journaling, etc.) Using Learning Analytics in agile learning environments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Centered Education</title>
      <link>/work/lex_professionalization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/lex_professionalization/</guid>
      <description>Professionalization of teachers and supporting students in learner centered education, LeX Applying Learning Analytics at the Open University Netherlands in partnership with Dipf University in Frankfurt in Germany and Delft University in The Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacherless Observations</title>
      <link>/work/teacherless_observations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/teacherless_observations/</guid>
      <description>For schools with the goal of student-directed learning, classroom observations of just students - without the teacher - provide a measure of progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools and Organizations</title>
      <link>/work/agile_educator_training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/agile_educator_training/</guid>
      <description>Agile Educator Training, Container4 Peak Challenges are activities for students to complete, autonomously, before teacher training in agility. Teachers can then reference their own students’ current experiences working autonomously during online training sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/history/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  A Brief History While we can rarely say that a way of thinking began with any one person at any particular time, a good starting point for what people often understand as agility is the creation in 2001 of the Agile Manifesto, a short statement of how work in software development might be both more agreeable and more effective.
Now, nearly twenty years later, working with the ideals and principles associated with agile is commonplace in certain sectors and increasingly applied in education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogs</title>
      <link>/services/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/blogs/</guid>
      <description>Blogs about Agile in Education Framed by the practices of EDgility and based largely on teaching and learning at a grade 7 to 12 Swiss boarding school.
Container4, Peak Challenges Framed by the practices of EDgility and based largely on teaching and learning at a grade 7 to 12 Swiss boarding school.
Teaching Your Way Around the World Hosted by the international educator, Paul Magnuson often blogs about topics in agile pedagogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Archives</title>
      <link>/services/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/archives/</guid>
      <description>The references marked with an asterisk (*) are found in Agile Methodologies in Education: A Review Bringing Methodologies from Industry to the Classroom.
2003* Paper recommending intro of agile methodology into software courses, based on positive reception of students
2005* Paper describing use of agile as an “educational technique” in a software class
March 2006* Changing computer science curriculum away from waterfall to agile
May 8, 2009 Paper from a Pace University Student Faculty Research Day showing how agile principles map to pedagogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts</title>
      <link>/services/podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Podcasts about Agile in Education
Agile in Education: Bill Tihen and Paul Magnuson of Leysin American School Jan 17, 2017
Integrum Education and Agile with John Miller January 10, 2013
Agile Amped, hosted by Howard Sublett Agile in Education: Bill Tihen and Paul Magnuson of Leysin American School Jan 17, 2017
Agile Amped, hosted by Howard Sublett Preparing the Next Generation for the New Agile World, Bret Thayer May 21, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/services/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/publications/</guid>
      <description>Allen, G. (2014). Cracking the Code to Teams: What Educators Can Learn from Programmers. EdSurge, (August 31).
Translating scrum for the classroom.
Breakspear, S. (?). Embracing Agile Leadership for Learning: How leaders can create impact despite growing complexity.
Embracing an agile mindset for school administrators.
Briggs, S. (2016). Agile Based Learning: What Is It and How Can It Change Education? InformED. February 22.
Scrum translated for pedagogy.
The eduScrum Guide: (2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools and Organizations</title>
      <link>/services/schools_organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/schools_organizations/</guid>
      <description>Schools using Agile in the Classroom and Organizations supporting Agile in the Classroom.
A group of agilists working in education created this graphic at their inaugural meeting in 2016. See also a video explanation.
The Agile in Education Compass A group of agilists working in education created this graphic at their inaugural meeting in 2016. See also a video explanation.
Agile in the Classroom Agile Learning Centers “Agile Learning Centers are an expanding network of intentional learning communities leveraging agile tools to support Self-Directed Education” Video introduction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
